miata.net 2010-11-26

# Privacy Policy

We do not share information acquired on Miata.net with any other party. The only exceptions to this policy are those cases where _**you**_ choose to make certain information publicly available. Examples of this include:

  1. **Classified ads  
**We publish your nickname,  and city in the ad along with the ad text. We do not publish your phone number unless you check the box asking that it be included in your ad. 

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal  
information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when  
you create a new user profile on the site to use specific features available only to  
registered users. 

The primary reason we obtain this information is to make the site easier for you to use by  
not having you enter information more than once. We may also periodically use your  
information to alert you to updated information and other new services from Miata.net  
Classifieds. 

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of  
Miata.net Classifieds. But you will not be able to access areas or use features that  
require registration.

  2. **Miata Forum  
**Anything you enter in the forum is publicly visible. We don't do anything with the information, but we can not prevent others from doing so.

  3. **Product Reviews**  
We publish the name and email address of the reviewer unless anonymity is requested. Anonymous reviews may or may not be published.

  4. **Email**  
Submissions, suggestions, comments, tech tips, photos, Miata of the Month, and other items which are sent in are occasionally published with the name and email address of the author. If you wish to remain anonymous in any email submission, please tell us. **We do not, under any circumstances, sell, trade, or give away email addresses or any other personal information gathered from Miata.net.**

Information may also be disclosed as a result of a court order or in response to law enforcement requirements.

#### THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

#### REGISTERED USER PROFILES 

When you register, your information is protected by use of a password which you select. Each person who registers must have a unique email address and user name. Duplicate profiles using the same email address or user name are not permitted. We highly recommend that you select a password which is neither common or known to others. We encourage you to NOT use information such as your Social Security Number, Phone Number or Date of Birth as your password. 

If you are a previous registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may only obtain it by email using our "Forgot Password" feature. Click the link on any login page to request your password be emailed to you. We cannot provide your password by any other means. 

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time. By following the "my profile" link provided on our system, you may view and edit personal information you have already given us. You may also elect to receive or discontinue receiving any email newsletters we may choose to distribute periodically. 

Any other exceptions will be specifically noted on the page itself. If you have any questions or require clarification of any portion of our privacy policy, please contact us.

* * *

* * *

* * *
